Hi, I'm Jaekang Kim from Sungkyungan University.
From now on, we'll talk about the basic concept of machine learning.
This is my first time, so I want to talk about just two things.
One is what is machine learning, and the other is the three types of machine learning.
So, shall we start?
And this is the whole content of today.
So I want to first talk about what is machine learning, and then I will share about three
types of machine learning, such as supervised learning, unsupervised learning, and reinforcement
learning.
So, what is machine learning?
Let's first talk about artificial intelligence.
It's the science and engineering of making intelligence machines.
And machine learning is a branch of artificial intelligence, so it's a sort of subset of
artificial intelligence.
And deep learning is also a famous concept, and it's also the subset of machine learning.
Actually, it is based on the neural network, which is one of the machine learning algorithms.
So, I want to talk about what is machine learning.
I can tell you that machine learning is to improve the performance of programs based
on given data, previous results, or experiences.
The main difference with the traditional programming is the